Bring it in.
Please sign here.
Okay. As you requested,
we deposited 600 million dollars into your account, sir.
You can now withdraw the entire balance...
whenever you like.
You became so wealthy at such a young age.
Was it hard work or luck?
(Reborn Rich)
(A week ago in Seoul)
(Episode 1)
("My Era, My Life, My Soonyang")
(Level 2 Computer-assisted Audit)
(Soonyang Group Family Tree)
We'll move onto the question on page 83.
Which of the following isn't true...
about marketable securities?
Equity security...
Equity security is another word for stocks.
- Here he comes. - Over here!
Manipulation of stocks, misconduct, and embezzlement.
Do you admit to the charges?
Prison time of 3 years with 5 years probation.
What is your take on the sentence?
Did you expect the court...
to grant probation in the second trial?
Do you have anything to say?
Are you certain there aren't any connections?
(Chairman Jin Young Ki borrowed-name account:)
(4.5 billion dollars)
I'm impressed, sir.
Your acting has gotten better.
You look good on camera too.
The justice department does its job well, doesn't it?
Fairly and justly.
Once again, the outcome was undoubtedly 3 and 5.
Prison time of 3 years with 5 years probation.
As long as you're wealthy enough,
a gracious chairman can get away with professional misconduct,
embezzlement,
and even tax evasion...
for a fixed price.
A fixed wholesale price of 3 years and 5 years.
It's like the crimes come with a price tag.
Why? Because there can't be a probational period...
for a sentence over three years.
Prosecutor Seo.
How will you proceed?
What can we do but adhere to the court's ruling?
What? Really?
We should respect the ruling...
and make an appeal with additional evidence.
We'll have him convicted and imprisoned.
Yes, of course.
South Korea is a constitutional state.
This isn't the Republic of Soonyang.
(Chairman Jin Yang Cheol Bust Unveiling Ceremony)
(In honour of Soonyang's objective that is fairness in business)
Just a second. Excuse me.
Hello, I'm Assistant Manager Shin Gyeong Min.
Hello, sir. I'm Assistant Manager Shin Gyeong Min.
Hello, I just transferred...
to the Future Asset Management Department
I'm Assistant Manager Shin Gyeong Min.
- Is that so? - Yes, sir.
(Jin Young Ki, Son Jeong Rae)
Please collect all products that are set on the table.
They will be replaced.
Is there an issue? None are past the expiration date.
Actually, I should first ask who you are.
The chairman is allergic to peaches.
He might lose consciousness from respiratory distress...
because of this beverage.
(Peach juice concentrate 2 percent)
(Shin Gyeong Min)
- Assistant Manager Shin. - Yes?
I'm Senior Manager Yoon Hyeon Woo...
of the Future Asset Management Department.
Yoon Hyeon Woo?
The one I've heard stories about?
I apologize for the belated greeting.
I'm Shin Gyeong Min, the newest member of your team.
We don't have time for that. Let us hurry.
Yes, sir.
- Remove those beverages. - Sure.
What should one do to be like you?
I hear the brutal workload...
has the average person quit in less than three years.
You're the only one who held out for more than five,
and you serve the chairman as one of his most trusted employees.
Allow me, sir.
I want to be just like you, Mr. Yoon.
Could you share some pointers? I'm a quick study, you see.
Let me see your phone.
Gosh, are we exchanging numbers?
It isn't one of Soonyang's.
I'll get a new one right away!
Could he be any sexier?
- Can you look this way? - Over here!
- Please look this way. - Can you look this way?
- Over here. - Sir, please.
- Could you look this way? - Sir, over here.
- Over here, please. - Please look this way.
- This way, please. - How have you been doing?
Attention. 1-0, 1-alpha are entering the building.
Let us hurry.
Mr. Yoon, what does "1-0" mean?
We are not allowed to refer to the chairman's family by name.
The chairman who is the eldest goes by 1-0,
and his wife is 1-alpha.
The vice-chairman goes by 2-0,
his wife is 2-alpha, and his daughter is 2-1.
And so on and so forth.
I have 1-1 and 1-2 travelling up from the parking lot.
What is it? What is this about?
Can't you give me a heads up?
The ceremony will soon commence.
I don't know what this is about, but tell him after the ceremony.
Don't you know who Father is having this ceremony for?
The press, prominent social figures,
and members of your exceptional family...
will be focused on you today.
Are you going to ruin it for yourself?
Sir.
Father!
The succession...
within Soonyang Group?
It won't go as planned.
Because I'm renouncing my inheritance.
What?
Shortly at 11am, we will commence the bust unveiling ceremony...
of Soonyang Group's founder, the late Chairman Jin Yang Cheol.
(Family, Jin Hwa Young)
We ask all guests present at the event...
to take their seats in order to ensure a peaceful ceremony.
We will soon commence the bust unveiling ceremony.
(Jin Seong Jun, Jin Young Ki, Son Jeong Rae)
The accident that day.
Did you think I would never find out?
- Seong Jun. - It's over, Father.
(Chairman Jin Young Ki)
Pride...
is only feared when someone is worthy enough.
How dare you renounce your inheritance!
Especially when you haven't earned even a penny...
on your own before.
The house you live in,
your car, your title, your wife,
and even your name.
What you have been enjoying...
were given to you by me, your grandfather, and Soonyang.
Pride...
is a luxury for only those...
who can actually leave the lifestyle behind.
You are not a man of such calibre.
No one knows that more than I do.
All I did...
was my best as your father.
It was for my sake, you say?
You...
have been suffocating me in the cruellest way.
That I'm not worthy.
That I'm not a man who can lead Soonyang.
You told me that in your own way...
by making that choice that day.
This is me living up to expectations.
Don't go.
Don't...
Chairman Jin, it's time.
Chairman Jin?
Chairman Jin, it's Yoon Hyeon Woo.
Sir!
Sir?
Send paramedics to the chairman's office.
This is an emergency.
Sir?
Sir!
Darn it.
Come on. Hurry!
You said Young Ki would be behind bars.
Never do you keep your promises.
Darn politicians.
Politics should be conducted on a broad perspective.
The whole nation shouldn't have to suffer...
from a family feud.
"Soonyang runs the South Korean economy."
Your family takes pride in that.
I'm close to witnessing Seong Jun's coronation...
at the ceremony designed to commemorate my father...
all while clapping my hands off.
It's why you should've supported me back then...
instead of your own family.
If you had done that,
it would've been you claiming the throne.
- No way. - Yes way.
- How mature of you. - I'm glad you noticed.
- Is it dementia you have? - You know nothing about...
Goodness, Director Kim.
So? What is this about?
Allow me to tell you inside.
What is this?
Why did you gather us in private?
The chairman is currently receiving emergency surgery...
for acute myocardial infarction.
What?
What about the unveiling ceremony?
We will proceed as planned.
Issuing a press release will hurt our stock price.
The special announcement...
should come from the chairman for it to be meaningful.
- Of course. - The chairman of a company...
who the prosecution just released...
was now met with a health issue.
Displaying lack of leadership won't help the business.
So?
Who should announce it instead?
Honey, did you bring another necktie?
It's in the car. Should I get it?
Yes.
Vice-Chairman Jin Seong Jun should give the announcement.
What?
The announcement.
The restructuring of the organization hierarchy...
may seem complex,
but the issue at hand is simple.
How will Soonyang resolve its issue...
surrounding the succession?
Don't they all want to see...
the vice-chairman step up to the plate?
The government, the people, and also our shareholders.
Don't you agree, Hyeon Min?
I hear you summoned me.
You never have to ask Mr. Yoon twice.
After the unveiling ceremony,
Soonyang will make a special public announcement.
Vice-Chairman Jin Seong Jun will be giving the speech.
The ceremony will be over in 30 minutes.
Wherever he went, you are to find him...
and bring him to me.
Time isn't a luxury we have, Mr. Yoon.
You must hurry.
If he isn't on the podium by that time,
you will no longer have a place at Soonyang.
The shortest route to the hotel will get you back in 20 minutes.
- I'll drive. - Sure.
The only problem is that the nearby department store...
is having a sales event, and it's lunch hour.
If we get stalled at the hotel,
thirty minutes won't be enough.
You should formally complain about the unreasonable task.
You said you wanted to be like me.
Of course.
- You wish for a long career. - Yes.
There are three things I never do.
Three things. Just a second.
I never reject orders made by the chairman's family.
I never ask questions, and...
I never make my own judgement.
Those are my rules.
Excuse me. Vice-Chairman Jin?
Vice-Chairman Jin?
Quiet.
I can hear them speak.
They can sense tremor on the sides of their bodies.
Right now, they're speaking loudly.
They want us to be quiet.
French cuisine...
made from seasonal ingredients will be served...
When in danger,
they send out a distress signal.
Do you know what it is?
If you're not interested, we will not serve lunch today.
Sir?
Vice-Chairman Jin?
Didn't I tell you to be quiet?
I just said it.
Please!
I ruined it.
I ruined it!
You knew the answer!
You will pee.
Just like now.
One, two, three!
Who called you smart when you are the opposite?
Why would you let Seong Jun make the announcement?
You'd only be solidifying his position at the company.
Don't you know that?
That'll only be true when he makes the announcement.
Are you saying he won't be here?
It'll be official.
Vice-Chairman Jin Seong Jun...
is a bit too dangerous to take on the mantle.
Darn it!
If you had been quiet,
none of this would've happened.
Once again, you think I'm the bad guy.
Why make me out to be one...
when you're the ones at fault?
Why?
Mr. Jin...
Mr. Yoon, are you all right?
Mr. Shin, escort everyone out.
Sure. Let us leave. Come on.
Oh, no.
This happened in 1987,
at the 60th birthday party for your grandfather,
former Chairman Jin.
You smashed the Goryeo celadon that he cherished...
and was scolded by him for the first time.
- What? - Not because of the celadon.
Because being driven by emotions...
wasn't an adequate quality in someone...
who were to run a business that is Soonyang.
- Mr. Yoon! - I read it...
in his autobiography.
Since that day, you honed his teachings...
and gave thought to the true qualities of a businessman.
That is how...
you were able...
to become the responsible and prudent businessman.
The PR team is putting together a press release.
You were only late to the unveiling ceremony...
because you stayed behind until the last second...
in order to cautiously reflect the late chairman's...
management philosophy...
in the announcement.
The ceremony ends...
in 12 minutes.
If you make it there by that time,
no one will take issue with today's events.
Wait for me outside.
The chairman is currently receiving emergency surgery.
What happened in that room before he collapsed...
will never become public knowledge.
For I...
will never talk.
You have ten minutes.
I only ask for your cooperation.
Promoting nonsense such as...
open-mind management...
has mutts barking at their owners, Mr. Yoon.
Have the car ready.
Thank you, Mr. Jin.
Thank you.
Gosh. I apologize for my tardiness.
Our Soonyang...
wishes to do its due diligence as one of Korea's top companies...
by being reliable and by meeting the ethical standard of the people.
Soonyang will be restructured as a holding company...
to improve asset quality...
which is an issue the group has been numerously...
called out on.
(Family)
I am well aware...
that Soonyang has been criticized for evading the law...
during its tumultuous former succession processes.
We will accept any criticism that comes our way,
and do our best to honestly answer...
to the needs of time.
Soonyang's innovation...
won't stay limited to its technology and products.
In that sense,
the huge amount of profit that will be levied...
as a result of the shares traded...
by all subsidiary companies during the transition...
will be paid faithfully and accurately.
That little brat.
What on earth is that brat blabbering about?
A business that'll benefit the nation.
Fairness in business.
I will honour the wishes of my grandfather,
former Chairman Jin Yang Cheol,
and let Soonyang be reborn as a company...
that is cherished by the people.
(Family)
Gyeong Min, you probably know.
Tell us.
What happened to Mr. Yoon's face?
As if you need to ask.
Everyone knows that 1-1 can be violent.
Even after the humiliation,
I bet he'll act all high and mighty...
as the senior manager at Soonyang.
Mr. Yoon.
He's incredible.
Not anyone can be the chairman's right-hand man.
He's no right-hand man.
A dirty glove he wears on his right hand, maybe.
You know, the cheap kind you wear...
to keep your hands clean that can be replaced at any time.
To be honest, he doesn't have the qualifications.
He was a handpicked high-school graduate.
They're easily done away with.
What qualified guy in the right mind would do what he does?
But look at Mr. Yoon. He stakes his life to serve.
He has to.
He's not good at much else.
(1-alpha)
Hello, ma'am, Yoon speaking.
Sorry for taking my time.
Yes, I understand. I'll be right over. Bye.
It's done, ma'am.
You know,
I feel uncomfortable, Mr. Yoon.
I know he has a carer,
but I'm stuck here as long as my husband is.
You know how particular I am about cleanliness.
Must I call and give instructions...
regarding minute details?
I apologize.
I was neglectful.
I'm not a stingy person, am I?
I know my manners.
Here.
Not at all. It's fine.
Go on.
Take it.
Yes?
Yes. Thank you.
(Soonyang Medical Center)
Hi, I'm late.
I'm leaving now.
Hyeon Woo. Have some braised ribs.
Your mom got spoiled today.
She got served by her eldest son.
You didn't make it last year,
and Mom waited for a while.
I tried to burn the prayer after the rite,
but it just wouldn't burn.
This is how it has always been.
Mom will understand.
Oh, I forgot to bring the soup.
Hyeon Woo.
Yes?
This is for you.
What is it?
I got my first paycheck.
You're working?
What about the civil service exam?
I quit studying for that.
If I couldn't pass for so long,
it's not meant to be.
I can't ask you to pay my expenses and classes forever.
Are you afraid I can't support you?
- It's not that. - Hyeon Min.
Do you think little of me too?
You've done more than enough for Dad and me.
Now I want to help out.
You've shouldered the burden so far.
Your brother has a point.
You should live for yourself now.
You may work at the greatest company in the country,
at a successful job working for the highest people there.
But you must have a family of your own...
to be able to call yourself a real man and a grown-up.
I should have a wife and kids, a family of my own?
Is that what made you a dignified man?
Father.
Do you have the right to say that to me?
It's Mom's death anniversary.
It's the anniversary of her death of all days.
- And you're saying... - Hyeon Woo.
Stop it.
Whatever.
You're leaving already?
Bye.
Hyeon Woo. Why not stay the night?
Hyeon Woo.
(Lawyer Son, Legal)
Move it, okay? You're too slow.
Let's be quick.
(Jeongsimjae 1F)
(Jeongsimjae 2F)
(Soonyang Group Family Tree)
(Late Jin Yang Cheol, Late Lee Pil Ok)
("My Era, My Life, My Soonyang")
Take all the files, even if they're double-sided.
- Empty all the drawers. - Okay.
Hurry up. Be quick.
Take the hard drives, files, everything.
Don't leave anything behind.
(Prosecutors' Office)
Who's in charge here?
Let's see the warrant.
Senior Manager Yoon Hyeon Woo, Future Asset Management Department.
Prosecutor Seo Min Yeong with the Anti-corruption Team.
Let's see the search and seizure warrant.
I'll take it.
We suspect Soonyang Chemicals and Soonyang World's window dressing...
was set up by Soonyang Corporation's Planning and Coordination.
The goal would be Vice-Chairman Jin Seong Jun's illegal takeover.
Soonyang does not bend or break any laws in the succession process.
As per the special statement that was read out yesterday.
I interpreted that differently.
"To be able to afford the massive amount of taxes..."
"that would occur in the process,"
"the owner family including Jin Young Ki..."
"and Jin Seong Jun have enough funds stashed aside."
It sounded like a confession to me.
And I couldn't ignore that confession.
- If we're done, let's go. - Okay.
Pack up. It's time to go.
The Future Asset Management Department?
That means the owner family is the future asset.
Do you really think so?
They call you "Soonyang's Grim Reaper."
Not only do you only wear black,
you indict anyone without a care...
if Soonyang's involved somehow.
Do you want to gain fame for taking Soonyang down or...
is there a personal vendetta others don't know about?
There's a lot of gossip about you.
I don't think it's either.
I think...
you're just doing your job as best you can.
The same goes for me as well.
Do you take special lessons?
You're quite eloquent.
(Prosecutors' Office)
(Seoul District Public Prosecutors' Office)
Is it true?
All the computers are new, never used once,
and other than the first few pages,
the files are printouts of PR stuff and of Soonyang's history.
It has to be that...
they knew we'd be coming and they were prepared.
- Mr. Shin. - Yes?
Planning and Coordination's seating chart.
Replace all the computers as assigned.
Yes, sir.
I sent a list of files to either keep or delete.
It's a sensitive job, so be extra careful.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Shin.
You got a new phone?
Oh, yes.
Mr. Yoon.
So...
I apologize. What happened yesterday...
I'm off to report to the Vice-Chairman.
Do you want to tag along?
Yes.
Prosecutors are so weird.
I said I'd abide by the law, and they attacked me first.
It makes me want to retaliate.
What's the likelihood of another search and seizure?
It is very unlikely.
I already gave Mr. Yoon the necessary instructions.
He'll work with Planning and Coordination,
and any problematic files...
will be carefully separated and deleted forever.
Even if prosecutors come by again,
they won't find anything illegal or suspicious, sir.
You do a good job.
Thank you.
(Soonyang Medical Center)
Who was that gentleman?
He's 4-0, Advisor Jin Yoon Ki.
Chairman Jin Yang Cheol's fourth son.
I didn't know the late chairman had a fourth son.
I heard he'd cut ties with the family for some reason.
- Mr. Shin? - Yes?
Oh, right.
Gosh.
Wasn't that ex-Miss Soonyang and movie star...
What was her name?
She's 4-alpha.
What? Then she's...
Yes. She's married to Advisor Jin Yoon Ki.
She's the exact reason he cut ties with the family.
That's crazy.
Do they have any children?
They have a son.
I heard 4-1 is into entertainment...
that's not tied to Soonyang.
He must be quite old.
I guess it pays to come from a great family.
His heart stopped twice during surgery,
so while administering CPR,
we inserted a stent in his aorta.
As a result, this morning, oxygen saturation was good,
and all numbers and levels have returned to normal.
Oh, thank you. Thanks so much.
- Thank you. - I must see him.
Right now, complete rest is the best medicine.
You cannot see him for a while.
Please cooperate.
Doctor Ahn.
Just a moment.
Hey. You still have that skill.
You startle people by showing up.
And you're still afraid.
If you have nothing, you fear nothing.
You should try harder, Auntie.
Did you call her? As if anyone misses her.
She doesn't even take my calls.
A long time has passed.
Am I still an unwelcome guest within the family?
- You know that and... - If you knew what I brought,
you couldn't mistreat me anymore.
Let's hear it.
What did you bring with you?
Three percent.
Three percent of Soonyang Corporation's shares.
Once Soonyang becomes a holding company,
when the time comes for you to fight over who becomes chairman,
won't my three percent be the casting vote?
What do you want instead?
My son.
I must know...
the truth behind the accident that day.
You all know!
Bring me the answer.
Then I'll hand over all I own.
Thank you.
Mr. Yoon, I need to talk to you about something.
Sure.
As you said, I separated the files to be discarded...
from the ones we should keep.
- The ones on the computer too? - Yes.
But I found something.
Well...
This wasn't on the list.
The thing is, it's an old document that is out of date.
At first, I was just going to dispose of it. But I saw...
a number of transactions involving large amounts in the span of years.
You should go through it and decide what to do with it.
(Confidential)
As you can see, Soonyang Micro...
is a dummy company that only exists on paper.
The records show large transactions between the company...
and Soonyang's subsidiaries that took place for over a decade.
Despite Soonyang Micro's transaction and sales records,
I could not find anything on the company...
in any of Soonyang's contracts and financial documents,
as if it had been hidden on purpose.
Do you...
realize what that means?
Someone is siphoning Soonyang's money overseas...
through this paper company, sir.
- Sir. - This is...
just a document that should've been disposed of long ago.
Had there been a problem,
Internal Affairs would've already dealt with it.
Do you think you're more competent...
than Soonyang's top-tier talent?
But this is clearly...
Mr. Yoon Hyeon Woo, the head of Future Asset Management.
Do you know why I've been keeping you on for the past five years?
You know exactly when to step in and when to back off. That's why.
So keep it up.
Do not make me repeat myself.
Got anything else to say?
No, sir.
I guess you had to work late, Mr. Yoon.
So? Have you finished organizing the documents?
Yes, sir.
It's been taken care of.
I'll be off, then.
(Chairman Jin Yang Cheol)
It was white porcelain.
My grandfather's vase that I broke.
It wasn't Goryeo celadon. It was a white porcelain vase.
But in his autobiography, he wrote that it was a Goryeo celadon vase.
I swear, he knew nothing about me.
You know more about me than he ever did.
My grandfather always said...
that Soonyang would go bust because of lazy fools like me.
But once again, he was wrong.
Sure, there are lazy fools like me at Soonyang.
But the company has employees like you as well.
You certainly deserve to wear the Soonyang badge.
About that day...
Thank you, Mr. Yoon.
Don't look at me like that. You should get going.
Yes, sir.
(Chairman Jin Yang Cheol)
Sir.
There's something I must tell you.
(Confidential)
Soonyang's assets are being siphoned...
into a paper company overseas in large amounts.
And the prosecution...
suspects that Soonyang has a large slush fund.
Once the prosecution finds out about the paper company,
the company will be charged...
with embezzlement, breach of duty, and tax evasion.
Also,
the plans for the holding company and the succession will be affected.
Then let me hear what you think I should do.
You should make a move before the prosecution does.
Submit a declaration of business closure for the paper company...
and make sure...
Soonyang Corporation absorbs the assets.
That's my suggestion, sir.
You found this in a cabinet in Planning and Coordination?
That's correct, sir.
Where is the original document?
Not these photos you took.
The original document.
Pardon me?
The original document...
Sir, Mr. Kim is here.
Okay.
Mr. Yoon brought something interesting.
(Confidential)
Go on.
Where's the original document?
Well...
I got rid of it, sir.
You did?
Yes, sir.
If the existence of the paper company comes to the surface,
someone...
will try to destroy all evidence. That's why...
I took and saved the photos and got rid of the original document.
You made a wise choice, Mr. Yoon.
I'd like to ask you something, Mr. Kim.
About this paper company, Soonyang Micro.
I bet you...
You knew about it, didn't you?
Pardon?
Answer wisely, Mr. Kim.
Sir, I...
If you knew but didn't report it, you either...
do not approve of me as your boss...
or became greedy for that money.
If you didn't know about it, that's even worse.
It means you're incompetent.
So which one is it?
I apologize, sir.
Either way, I now know that you've betrayed Soonyang.
- Mr. Yoon. - Yes, sir.
- You have a valid passport, right? - Yes.
As of today, you're the senior finance manager...
of the Planning and Coordination Department.
Go retrieve Soonyang's assets that have been siphoned off overseas.
That is your first mission as the senior finance manager.
I trust that you'll do a good job.
I'll do my best, sir.
I've done some thinking, Father.
You were right.
So now,
I must have something to my name.
The new Soonyang and its glowing future will be mine.
Soonyang's dark past shall perish with you, Father.
Until the succession is completed,
just keep on breathing like this.
Please sign here.
Okay. As you requested,
we deposited 600 million dollars into your account, sir.
You can now withdraw the entire balance...
whenever you like.
You became so wealthy at such a young age.
Was it hard work or luck?
Then let me hear what you think I should do.
You should make a move before the prosecution does.
Submit a declaration of business closure for the paper company...
and make sure...
Soonyang Corporation absorbs the assets.
That's my suggestion, sir.
Vice-Chairman Jin Seong Jun.
Do you think you can indict him?
Hey, where are you going?
Is this the right way?
Don't worry. This is the shortcut.
Only we know. Taxi drivers.
We're almost there.
Okay.
One minute left.
Hey!
Hey! Help!
Hey...
Are you okay? Let me help you up.
Sorry.
The 600 million-dollar slush fund.
The slush fund created through Soonyang Micro.
I heard Yoon Hyeon Woo went to retrieve and launder the money.
Ye Jun.
Who told you such nonsense?
Our finance director.
Do you want to meet him?
Director Kim.
Then the slush fund...
Once it's retrieved,
can I have it?
Ye Jun, you've grown a lot.
Mr. Shin.
Why are you here?
Why in the world... Why are you doing this to me?
You told me...
to never...
disobey the higher-ups' orders or ask questions.
You said I should never make my own judgement.
I simply...
followed your advice.
Let go.
Let go!
Who is it?
Who ordered you to do this?
The person who needs this.
Do Jun, you woke up?
What? 4-alpha?
We're almost there. Time to wake up.
That's 4-0.
Hey, what are you doing?
Hey, then you must be 4-1.
What? "Hey?"
You little...
Am I alive?
Why do I look...
What happened to me?
Do you want to know?
Shall I tell you?
It's obvious at a single glance.
Why?
Why am I here?
- Do Jun. - What is it? What's wrong?
It wasn't me.
I didn't do anything!
Where is this place?
(Gwanghwamun)
The National Museum of Korea?
Today marks a historic moment when the demolition...
of the Japanese General Government Building commenced.
Gyeongbokgung will be restored...
That building was demolished in 1995.
How is it still there?
Do Jun, are you all right?
(The 24th Trade Day Business Medal Reward Ceremony)
(Sejong Center for the Performing Arts)
Are you all right?
Let's go say hi to Grandma.
Let's go.
(The 24th Trade Day Business Medal Reward Ceremony)
Hey, Yoon Ki.
Hello.
Oh, Yoon Ki. There you are.
Hyeong Jun, Do Jun. You're here too.
Come to Grandma!
Hello.
My gosh. You're a big boy now.
This can't be.
Oh, my. You're a man now.
You people are...
Mr. Chairman is here.
Welcome.
Congratulations, sir.
Congratulations.
- Congratulations. - Congratulations, sir.
Hello.
- Congratulations, sir. - Congratulations, sir.
Chairman Jin Yang Cheol?
The founder of Soonyang.
It's him.
Chairman Jin Yang Cheol.
(Reborn Rich)
Who am I?
What kind of question is that?
You are Jin Do Jun, the youngest grandchild of the Soonyang family.
This can't be.
Does it make money?
Will it help Soonyang?
Between DJ and YS, choose the one who's more likely to win.
Who would that be?
If it were me, I'd back Roh Tae Woo's campaign.
Did you eavesdrop on the adults' conversation?
You little...
Throw salt after them.
There are beggars everywhere.
It's not a prank. It's true.
By any chance, do you know what the future holds?
Answer me!
One of these people...
killed me.